Upgraded is a romance, comedy film directed by Carlson Young.
Ana is an ambitious intern dreaming of a career in the art world
while trying to impress her demanding boss Claire.
When she's upgraded to first class on a work trip, she meets handsome Will, and Ana pretends to be her boss– a white lie
that sets off a glamorous chain of events, romance and opportunity, until her fib threatens to surface.
Ana, played by Camila Mendes.
William, played by Archie Renaux.
Claire, played by Marisa Tomei.
Catherine, played by Lena Olin.
Julian Marx, played by Anthony Stewart Head.
Arnold Grant, played by Thomas Kretschmann.
Upgraded is a 2024 American romantic comedy film directed by Carlson Young and starring Camila
Mendes, Archie Renaux, Thomas Kretschmann, Grégory Montel, Lena Olin and Marisa Tomei.
The film is a modern-day retelling of the classic fairytale "Cinderella" and focuses on Ana Santos, an ignored-but-ambitious intern in the
New York art world whose life and career change when by happenstance she is upgraded to first class on a flight to London.
It was released on Amazon Prime Video on February 9, 2024.
The film explores themes of new york city, london, england,
mistaken identity, life's dream, falling in love.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.